# SANTOSH JHA

#### | Delhi | 8299519708 |

Email: <u>Santoshjhavns@gmail.com</u>

Portfolio: <a href="http://santosh0954.github.io/Portfolio/">http://santosh0954.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

## **OBJECTIVES**

Goal-oriented Web Designer brings a strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Develop websites and designs that are custom-crafted and focused on customers with the help of various web design packages. I have been committed to providing a great user experience, usability, and speed for multiple users for more than one year.

## **EXPERIENCE**

May 2022 – Dec 2022 : Web designer (Freelance)

Jan 2023 – Feb 2024: Web Designer

(Mannat Technology, Prayagraj, Varanasi)

### **PROJECTS**

Admin Panel: Admin panel design for managing customer and services

with responsive and modern design.

(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass, Bootstrap)

Link: <a href="https://santosh0954.github.io/CRM/src/">https://santosh0954.github.io/CRM/src/</a>

Admin Panel: It is an admin panel design for a company who manages

Their products data and telecom related customers. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass, Slick Carousel)

Link: https://santosh0954.github.io/CRM/src/

Taxi Booking: Online Taxi booking website design for development

company for business purposes.

(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Sass, Slick Carousel)

Link: https://santosh0954.github.io/taxiBooking/src/

Online Stories reading: Online Reading Stories website like Pratilipi website

functionality, It is a fully responsive design for all modern

Devices.

(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Sass, Slick Carousel)

Link: https://santosh0954.github.io/sahityaKriti/src/

## **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

Tech Stack: HTML-5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap,

Material-UI, Tailwinds.css, React, Redux, Node.js,

Typescript, Mongo DB, MySQL, Git & GitHub, Webpack, Gulp

Application: Visual Studio Code, Photoshop, FileZilla

## **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2022: MCA

## COMMUNICATION

Excellent in reading/writing and speaking Hindi and English as well as understand almost all local dialects of Central northern India.

Thank You